You reacted to the sound, now.
音に反応したね、今
I'm glad it turned out like this.
こうなったのが良かったな
Yahoo.
やっほー
Thank you for keeping this up.
このままありがとうね
What do you think?
どうですか?
Since then.
あれから
I spend my days without anything.
僕に何もなく日常を過ごしてます
Haven't you found out?
バレてない?
It's now.
今だ
I haven't found out yet.
まだバレてないです
I'd like to be told that I look like an adult.
大人っぽいって言われたいですね
That's right.
そうですよね
Maybe someone has fallen in love with it.
好きになった人が多分
Didn't you say that?
言ってませんでした?
Leave it like this.
このまま
I didn't say that.
言 ってませんでした
It was interesting.
面白かったね
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
You reacted to the sound, now.
音に反応したね、今
I'm glad it turned out like this.
こうなったのが良かったな
Yahoo.
やっほー
Thank you for staying this way.
この ままありがとうね
What do you think?
どうですか?
Since then.
あれから
I spend my days without anything.
僕に何もなく日常を過ごしてます
Haven't you found out?
バレてない?
It's now.
今だ
Haven't found out yet
まだバレてない
is.
です
I was worried.
心 配だったよ
Nothing happened.
何事もなく
I'm so happy.
嬉しいな
It would be tough if my boyfriend found out.
彼氏なんかにバレたら大変だから
I'm scared.
怖がれます
Will you hate me?
嫌がれちゃう?
I'm hated.
嫌がれちゃいます
If you were a cute girl like you, you would be bound.
君みたいな可愛い子だったらね、 束縛されるよね
Is it immediate head?
即頭ですか?
yes.
はい
I was immediately turned on.
即頭されちゃいました
Compared to my uncle.
おじさんと比べて
Yeah, I feel like that.
うん、って感じ
Did you have a sex friend?
セフレとはありました?
There are no sex friends included.
セフレは入ってないです
Hasn't it gotten better since then?
あれから合ってないですか?
It doesn't match.
合ってないです
The outfit suits you.
似合ってます、服装
thank you.
ありがとうございます
It really suits me so well it's scary.
本当に似合いすぎて怖いですよ
They say I'm childish.
子供っぽいって言われる
No, I'd like to be told that I look like an adult.
いや、大人っぽいって言われたいですね
That's right.
そうですよね
Did you play any sports?
何かスポーツしてましたっけ?
TRUE?
本当?
Have you been walking around today dressed like that?
その格好で今日ずっと歩いてきたの?
yes.
はい
Couldn't you see it?
見られなかった?
yes.
はい
The person I fell in love with probably didn't say that.
好きになった人が多分、 言ってませんでした、
Before this.
この前
That's what I said.
言ってました
That was interesting, huh?
面白かったね、あれ
I would like to ask the princess, what kind of penis shape do you like?
姫さんに聞きたいんですけどね、 どんなおチンチンの形が好き
What?
なん ですか?
I had never thought about it.
考えたこともなかったです
I just didn't understand.
ちょっとわからなかった
Let's wait a moment, you two.
ちょっと待ちましょうか、2人で
yes.
はい
I'll turn on the camera and light.
カメラ、電気つけちゃいますよ
Is it a little dazzling?
ちょっと眩しいですか?
It's a little dazzling.
ちょっと眩しいです
What is that on the right?
その右にあるのが何ですか?
Is that it?
それですか?
Instead of Pepsi, I got Dr. Pepper.
私、ペプシーじゃないと、 ドクター・ペッパーをもらいました
not much.
あまり
Somehow, cola is normal.
なんか、コーラは普通に
Same red, but different.
同 じ赤だけど、違う
Will you see it?
見ます?
Hey, it's like this.
ちょっと、こうなってます
Isn't it cute?
可愛くない?
It's cute.
可愛いよ
So cute.
すごい可愛い
She's shy, after all.
シャイだね、やっぱり
Yeah, it's pretty good.
うん、なんかよくよ
I think I'll take it off for a moment.
ちょっと、脱いちゃおうかな
A little lighter.
ちょっと軽く
Good luck, can't you see?
頑張って、見えない?
Just try it on your hands and see.
ちょっと、手溶けてみて、じゃあ
Oh, nice.
おー、いいね
No, that's fine though.
いや、それでいいけど
watch?
視聴?
That's fine though.
いいけどよ
You can see it already.
それはもう、見えますよ
Can you see it?
見えます?
Yeah.
うん
It was a little stiff here.
ちょっと、ここ、硬かった
watch?
視聴?
Yeah.
うん
I saw it today too.
見えたね、今日も
Do you like it?
好きな?
These lewd pants.
こういうスケベなパンツが
But this is not like that.
でも、これは、そんなではない
Was this normal for me?
これは、私、普通だったの?
That's what I thought.
って思ってた
Most of the time, kids from the countryside really forget.
だいたい、田舎の子は本当に、忘れてんだから
Is it normal in the countryside?
田舎では普通?
usually.
普通
Are kids from the countryside more perverted?
田舎の子の方が、変態なのかな?
Maybe so.
そうかも
Wow.
うわー
If you make a decision like that, if you give it time,
そんな判断とかかったら、時間されたら、
It's going to be a big deal.
大変なことになるよ
almost.
だいたい
Isn't there a lot of things?
だいたいことない?
Try taking off the mask while maintaining your posture.
そのまま、体勢維持しながら、マスク取ってみて
Throw it away and set it aside.
捨てといて、横に
Yeah.
うん
Please leave the desk next to you.
横の机、置いといてみて
chain.
チェーン
I'm used to it.
なれてるよ
It's insanely big.
めちゃくちゃ大きい
You're going to do something amazing, right?
すごいことするんでしょ?
Look behind you.
後ろを見て
Get your hands on it, there.
手ついてみて、そこ
Do you like the sound of uncle?
おじさんの音好き?
Are you licking me often?
よく舐めてあげてんの?
Yeah.
うん
Just leave it to uncle.
おじさんだけにして
Yeah.
うん
good?
いい?
Yeah.
うん
Go in the middle and make it visible to this camera behind you.
真ん中入って、後ろのこのカメラに見えるようにして
Ah, there it is.
あー、あっちゃったね
Ah, yes, yes.
あー、そうそうそう
Oh, that's amazing.
あー、すごいよ
It's already too intense and I'm going to go.
もう激しくて、おじさんいっちゃうから
Ah, let's go.
あー、いく